[
  {
    "question": "melon",
    "answers": ["лодка", "аукцион", "дыня", "соседний"],
    "right" : 3
  },
  {
    "question": "parcel",
    "answers": ["сверток", "семья", "воздух", "скрывать"],
    "right" : 1
  },
  {
    "question": "snail",
    "answers": ["улитка", "змея", "ноготь", "ковер"],
    "right" : 1
  },
  {
    "question": "heaven",
    "answers": ["день", "небеса", "просить", "лодка"],
    "right" : 2
  },
  {
    "question": "fence",
    "answers": ["забор", "составлять", "потребление", "дипломат"],
    "right" : 1
  },
  {
    "question": "dawn",
    "answers": ["протестант", "центр", "холодный", "рассвет"],
    "right" : 4
  },
  {
    "question": "edge",
    "answers": ["экспонат", "отец", "край", "сложный"],
    "right" : 3
  },
  {
    "question": "state",
    "answers": ["выше", "отличие", "пыльный", "состояние"],
    "right" : 4
  },
  {
    "question": "jet",
    "answers": ["лачуга", "способность", "изменять", "блестящий черный цвет"],
    "right" : 4
  },
  {
    "question": "thought",
    "answers": ["потребление", "электронный", "гриль", "мысли"],
    "right" : 4
  },
  {
    "question": "melon1",
    "answers": ["лодка", "аукцион", "дыня", "соседний"],
    "right" : 3
  },
  {
    "question": "parcel1",
    "answers": ["сверток", "семья", "воздух", "скрывать"],
    "right" : 1
  },
  {
    "question": "snail1",
    "answers": ["улитка", "змея", "ноготь", "ковер"],
    "right" : 1
  },
  {
    "question": "heaven1",
    "answers": ["день", "небеса", "просить", "лодка"],
    "right" : 2
  },
  {
    "question": "fence1",
    "answers": ["забор", "составлять", "потребление", "дипломат"],
    "right" : 1
  },
  {
    "question": "dawn1",
    "answers": ["протестант", "центр", "холодный", "рассвет"],
    "right" : 4
  },
  {
    "question": "edge1",
    "answers": ["экспонат", "отец", "край", "сложный"],
    "right" : 3
  },
  {
    "question": "state1",
    "answers": ["выше", "отличие", "пыльный", "состояние"],
    "right" : 4
  },
  {
    "question": "jet1",
    "answers": ["лачуга", "способность", "изменять", "блестящий черный цвет"],
    "right" : 4
  },
  {
    "question": "thought1",
    "answers": ["потребление", "электронный", "гриль", "мысли"],
    "right" : 4
  }
]
